孩子们 2009年的冬天\n我和你们Robin阿姨成为了室友
Kids, in the winter of 2009, Aunt\nRobin and I had just become roommates.
坦白说 我们处得不是很好
And to be honest, it\nwasn't going very smoothly.
好好吃的样子 我也来点
Ooh, that looks good.\nI'm gonna get some.
没有牛奶了
There's no more milk.
不对啊 我刚在冰箱见到一罐
No, I just saw some in tin the fridge.
- 那是空的\n- 那就扔了它啊
- Empty.\n- So throw it out.
垃圾桶满了
The trash can's full.
那就把垃圾拿出去啊
So take the trash out.
我在吃麦片呢
I'm eating cereal.
知道不 当我让你跟我一起住时
You know, when I asked\nyou to be my roommate,
我在想 她是个女孩\n应该会很整洁吧
I figured, She's a girl, she'll be neat.
可是恰恰相反\n你简直像里的食尸鬼
But no, you're Ogre from\nRevenge of the Nerds.
听着 Ted
You know what, Ted?
先抛下刚刚发生的这件\n不具代表性的事不谈
Instead of coming up with hot off the\npress topical references like that,
或许你可以花一丁点时间去...\n怎么说呢 洗一下盘子 就一次也好
maybe you should spend a little time,\nI don't know, uh, washing a dish ever.
不好意思 我不能
Oh, darn, I can't.
我忙到忘了\n给换厕纸的魔法小精灵留一盘饼干了
I'm too busy leaving a plate of cookies for the\nmagical elf who changes the toilet paper roll.
等等 那不是小精灵\n从来都是我换的!
Oh, wait, there's no\nelf. It's always me!
从来都是我换的 你没换过!
I always change it. You never do!
- 没可能! 最后这五次都是我换的\n- 才不是呢 我昨天进去过...
- That is ridiculous!I changed it, like, the last five times.\n- No, I went in there yesterday...
停! 停下来! 老天 发生什么事了?
Stop! Stop! God, what is going on?
我们还在拍拖的时候
When we were dating each other,
基本上住在一起了 都没发生过这种事
we were practically living together and\nwe didn't drive each other this crazy.
我知道啊 怎么回事了?
I know. What happened?
知道为什么不? 我们那时有做爱
You know what it is? We were having sex.
男人和女人住在一起就必须要做爱
Men and women need sex to live together.
做爱能解决所有争论
It solves all disputes.
就像Barney说的那个世界和平理论?
Oh, like Barney's\ntheory about world peace?
所以我就跟她解释咯 我说 Madeline
So I explained to her.I said, Madeline,
每一个国际冲突\n从根本来说都是性关系紧张引起的
every single international conflict\nessentially boils down to sexual tension.
每个国际冲突?
Every international conflict?
每一个 兄弟
Every single one, dude.
所以说可以解决中东危机的是...
So the crisis in the Middle\nEast could be solved by...
加沙地带的脱衣舞娘 下一个
Gaza Strippers. Next.
南非种族隔离呢?
Apartheid?
岔开的大腿啊(种族隔离谐音) \n还能是什么?
Apart thighs. What else you got?
冷战呢?
Cold War?
戈尔巴乔夫夫人 脱~下~裤子
Mrs. Gorbachev, take down those pants.
看来我们只能谈谈情 说说性了
Well, guess we should just\nstart having sex, then.
没错
Yeah, right.
我明白
I know.
就像骑自行车一样 是吧? 伙计
It's like riding a bike, huh, buddy?
或者说骑着部颠簸的自行车
Riding a bike upside down, maybe.
听着 这只是偶然事件 \n我们谁也不能告诉
Okay, listen. If this is gonna happen on\noccasion, we can't tell anyone about this. Deal?
- 一言为定\n- 一言为定
- Deal.\n- Deal.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第12集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode12
- Marshall Marshall...
- 你们两个到底在干什么?
- Marshall, Marshall...\n- What the hell are you guys doing?
你们两个要 复合了?
What, are you guys, like, back together?
不 我们只是随便搞搞\n为了不再吵架而已
No. We're just having\nsexe don't fight anymore.
太好了 不 真的要对你们竖起大拇指了
Oh, that's a great idea. No,\nreally. Two thumbs up, guys.
嘿 我刚刚看见未来了\n你们这样真的对大家都好
Hey, I just looked into the future and that\nworks out really great for eve for everyone.
那你又在这里干什么?
What are you even doing here?
我正准备上班 然后要经过这里来...
I was on my way to work and I\njust had to drop by here to...
看杂志
read this magazine.
在...那头的房间看
In... that room over there.
我懂了
Oh, I get it.
没问题 哥们儿
No problem, buddy.
呃 有问题 哥们儿
Uh, yes, a problem, buddy.
你走这么大一段路来这里看杂志?
You came all the way over\nhere to read a magazine?
我敢说你上班那儿肯定能有地方看杂志
I'm willing to bet that there is\na place to read a magazine at work.
你知道 门上贴着个小男人的房间?\n（厕所）
You know, a room with a\nlittle man on the door?
行了 Robin 你就别这样了
Okay, Robin. Come on.
没人喜欢上班时看杂志的
Nobody likes to read a magazine at work.
我是说 如果你拿着本杂志走出办公室
I mean, you walk out of your\noffice holding a magazine
那本杂志就只说明一件事
and that magazine is saying\none thing and one thing only.
嘿 大家看呐 看看Marshall要干啥!
Hey everyone, look at what\nMarshall's about to do!
Marshall 正准备在\n大家都用的厕所里看旧杂志呢
Marshall's about to read a big ol' magazine\nin the bathroom that you all share with him.
那你有没想过只是草草的看一眼了事?
Well, have you thought about maybe not\nreading a magazine when you read a magazine?
看杂志怎么可以略过内容
You gotta read a magazine.
杂志就是让人好好读的嘛
I mean, that's why there's magazines.
不然的话 过去的时间不会再回来啊
Otherwise,t's just time\nyou're not getting back.
没错
Exactly.
更糟糕的是 从我办公室到厕所的那段路
And the worst part is this: That stretch\nof hallway from my door to that restroom
充满了鄙视的目光
is a gauntlet of judging eyes.
我老板的鄙视
You got my boss.
你要去做什么我们全知道了
We all know exactly\nwhat you're about to do.
她老板
Her boss.
嘿 Eriksen \n你怎么不直接把办公桌搬进去呢?
Hey, Eriksen, why don't you\njust move your desk in there?
还有Donald那种\n"不敢相信他这样还能找到老婆"的眼神
I-Can't-Believe-He-Has-A-Wife\nDonald.
小甜心 你太明显了啦~
Oh, sweetie, so obvious.
不管怎么说 我还是喜欢在这里看
Anyways, I just would\nrather do that here.
不 很不好意思 这是我们的房子
No, I'm sorry. This\nis our apartment now.
Marshall 你要看杂志就去其他地方
Marshall, you have to read\na magazine someplace else.
- 把钥匙给我\n- 好...难了 没门儿
- Give me your key.\n- Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
Marshall\nMarshall.
我刚刚好记起件事 是某三人间的秘密
I seem to recall a deal being\nstruck between three parties
没人希望泄露出去的秘密
wherein none would discuss a\ncertain event that transpired.
是关于...的秘密
An event of the... persuasion.
那把钥匙 女士 算是封口费了
That key, madam, buys my silence.
祝你们俩继续愉快
Good day to you both.
你们俩搞上了?
You two hooked up?
多谢你了 Lily
*****
这么说 你们俩...睡在一起了
So, wow. You two... slept together.
真是衰...帅啊 太帅了
That is awf... some. Awfsome.
干得好 Ted 上了她
Nice work, Ted. Tap that.
你们太小题大做了
It sounds like a bigger deal than it is.
我们好好商量了一下\n发现大家这几个月来都过的不太好
Yeah, we talked it over and we both\nrealized we've had a rough couple of months.
大家应该乐一乐
We deserve a little fun.
不对 这样会毁掉你们的友情的
No. This could wind up\nruining your friendship.
当前任之间想"随便乐一乐"\n最后肯定会有人受伤的
When two exes try to "just be casual,"\nsomeone always winds up getting hurt.
后来发现 Lily说对了
Turned out, Lily was right.
不过好戏在后头
But more on that later.
伙计们 这些我们都谈过了
Look, guys, we've got\nthis covered, okay?
没人会受伤的
No one's gonna get hurt.
我们还定下了规矩
We set up ground rules.
好吧 第一 这绝对只是肉体关系
Okay, rule number one: This is\nstrictly a physical relationship.
不带任何感情的 行不?
There are no feelings involved, okay?
废话 那不等于叫Fonz酷一点吗?\n(Fonz的男主角 被认为该剧中最酷的角色)
Oh, please, that's like\ntelling the Fonz to be cool.
还有因为这只是肉体关系 \n我们不用浪漫啥的 对不?
And since it's just physical, we don't\nhave to worry about romance, right?
那当然 我们可以边做边看电视啊!
Hell, no. Ooh, we can\ndo it while we watch TV!
太对了! 我们可以一心二用
Totally! And we can multi-task.
就像用做爱来调剂其他无聊的活动
You know, use the sex to spice\nup otherwise dull activities.
- 例如叠衣服\n- 算账单时
- Like folding laundry.\n- Paying bills.
做饭时
Cooking dinner.
- 好像不太卫生的样子\n- 是啊 不要那个
- That doesn't seem hygienic.\n- Yeah, not that one.
现在我们一搞上 就不再吵架了
And now that we're hooking\nup, we're not fighting anymore.
问题解决了
Problem solved.
事实上 这还是Barney的功劳
Actually, the credit belongs to Barney.
这事儿是拜你的世界和平理论所赐啊
This whole idea came out of\nyour thing about world peace.
没错 谢谢你啊 Barney  你说对了 \n和平理论是有效的 再次验证了
Yeah. Thanks, Barney. You were\nright. Peace was achieved. Repeatedly.
这么说是我 我让你们...
So I'm-I'm responsible for...
好极了 好极了 好极了
Excellent. Excellent. Excellent.
下一轮算我的!
next round's on me!
- 嘿 你没事吧\n- 没事 怎么这么问?
- Hey, are you okay?\n- Yeah. Why do you ask?
因为你流泪了
Well, for one thing,\nyou're openly weeping.
开心的眼泪
With joy.
我太为他们两个高兴了
So happy for those two.
Barney 承认吧
Barney, admit it.
你对Robin依然有感觉 \n这事让你伤心透了
You still have feelings for\nRobin and this is killing you.
我完全没事
I am totally fine.
好了 我失陪一下
Now, excuse me for just a minute.
我完全没事
I'm totally fine.
Barney 你要学会释放你的感情
Barney, you have to learn\nhow to express these feelings.
去跟心理医生谈谈吧
Maybe you should talk to a psychiatrist.
拜托
Please.
如果我要给个女人\n每小时200美元让我感觉好点
If I'm gonna pay some woman $200\nan hour to make me feel better,
那不可能只谈话
we aren't going to be talking.
我们都会在那个沙发上
And we're both going\nto be on that couch.
在这个故事里那女人是个妓女
The woman in this\nscenario is a prostitute.
一个淫乱的 \n衣冠不整的 隆过胸的东欧...
A dirty, skanky, surgically\nenhanced, Eastern European...
我明白
I got it.
这种不用当真的关系 \n还给了我们释放自我的机会
And there's something kind of liberating\nabout not taking it all too seriously.
昨晚 我边回电话边做了呢
Yeah. Last night, we actually did it while\nI was returning a bunch of phone calls.
我就知道你没有在用什么划船练习器
I knew you didn't get a rowing machine!
太棒了 这个话题还没完!
Awesome, we're still talking about this!
听着 这是我和Ted之间的私事
Look, guys, this is a private\nthing between me and Ted.
私事
Private Thing.
如果不是Marshall不能上班时看杂志\n我们都不会谈这件事
We wouldn't even be talking about this\nif Marshall could read a magazine at work.
他就这样 还记得在法学院那时不?
Oh, he's always been this\nway. Remember law school?
当然
Sure do.
宝贝? 宝贝 你怎么了?
Baby? Baby, what is it?
信用卡账单今天寄来了
The credit card bill came today.
你星期二时在\n隔学校两条街的酒店开了间房
You checked into a hotel two\nblocks from school on a Tuesday.
事情不是你想象那样的
It's not what you think.
她是谁? Marshall 她叫什么名字?
Who is she, Marshall? What's her name?
Burrito Carnitas Burrito(杂志名?)
Burrito. Carnitas Burrito.
这么说你在酒店开房\n只是为了可以在那里看杂志?
So, you checked into a hotel room just\nso you could read a magazine there?
嘿 Robin 不如我帮你看看女侍应那里\n有没大方糖喂给你的大马(傲慢的态度)?
Hey, Robin, do you want me to see if the waitress has\nany giant sugar cubes for that high horse of yours?
没人喜欢上班时看杂志的 \n如果有人说喜欢 那他就不是人类了
Nobody likes to read a magazine at work and if\nthey say that they do, then they're not human.
兄弟 我每天都在上班时看杂志的
Dude, I read a magazine\nat work every day.
我因为"看杂志"而迟到的会议不计其数
I can't tell you how many meetings I've been\nlate to because I was busy "reading a magazine."
可是我从来不内疚 那是我的时间
But I don't feel bad\nabout it. That's my time.
当然 "看杂志"不怎么光彩\n可那是我必须要做的事
Sure, "reading a magazine" ain't pretty,\nbut, you know, it's something I gotta do.
有什么可羞于启齿的
So why be ashamed about it?
等等 "看杂志"的意思就是打飞机 对不?
Wait, "reading a magazine"\nmeans masturbating, right?
太恶劣了 你又喝光我的牛奶
I can't believe it. You\ndrank all my milk again!
- 来做爱吧\n- 没问题
- We can have sex.\n- Okay.
这决定真是太棒了
It's the perfect set up.
每次我们要吵架了 就用做爱代替
Anytime we start getting into an\nargument, we just have sex instead.
一分钟前我们还在干架 而下一分钟后...
One minute we're just laying into\neach other, and then the next minute...
还是在"干架"哦
Well, same thing.
帅啊
Awesome.
今天早晨 她在门外吼我
So, this morning, she's\nyelling at me through the door,
你冲凉冲太久啦!
You're taking too long in the shower!
接着 她就自个儿跳进来了
Next thing I know, she hops in.
现在她都不介意我占她时间了
Now baby don't mind I took my time.
太帅了
So awesome.
不好意思我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
刚刚在Scherbatsky那儿"堵塞"了一下
I was just jammin' on Scherbatsky.
她用光了我的邮票 \n然后长话短说 邮递员都"敲"两次门了
She used up all my stamps, so long\nstory short, the postman rang twice.
一定要贺一下吧!
You must bump this!
真是太...
That's just so...
失陪一会
Excuse me for a second.
你是说等离子适合于低光环境\n而液晶就适合打游戏咯?
So, you're saying plasmas are better for\nlow light, but LCDs are better for games?
没错 不过彩显黑色还原性好
Right, but the CRTs\nhave the truest blacks.
如果说我追求明晰的对比率的话...
So, if I want a really\ncrisp contrast ratio...
彩显的单元像素结构\n表现出来的分辨率绝对比不上液晶
The CRT's deep-pixel cell structure produces\na resolution you just can't match with an LCD.
那我要彩显
I'll take the CRT.
Barney 真是太疯狂了
Barney, this is nuts.
我没事儿 谢谢
I'm doing just fine, thank you.
不 你的问题很严重
No, you're not.
你要学会放手
You need to learn to let this stuff out.
就像我幼稚园班里\n每星期二早上的"释放感情时间"一样
Like we do in my kindergarten class\nFeelings Hour every Tuesday morning.
听着 Lily 你幼稚园的小朋友
Look, Lily, maybe your\nkindergartners are upset that
也许会因为他们的朋友\n互相搞上了而心烦 但我不会
their friends are sleeping\nwith each other, but not me.
我好得不得了
I have never been better.
与此同时 \nMarshall依然在工作岗位上挣扎着
Meanwhile, Marshall was\nstill struggling at work.
都过来看看呐
Coming through.
今早加餐咯
Big breakfast this morning.
你们知道这是什么意思
You know what that means.
然后传来了他听说已久的好消息
But then came the best news\nhe'd heard in a long time.
你听说了吗?
And did you hear?
他们八楼办公室的人全被炒了
They laid off everybody\non the eighth floor.
我知道 现在那儿就是一座空城了
I know. It's a ghost town down there.
- 早\n- 早
- Morning.\n- Morning.
嘿 昨晚真刺激
Hey, that was fun last night.
没错 昨晚确实很享受
Word, that was a good one.
牢记在心: 别总将披萨盒乱扔
Mental note: don't throw\nout the pizza box more often.
好了 再见
All right, see you later.
昨晚 Robin把披萨盒扔在地上\n所以我们就做了3回
So, last night, Robin left a pizza box out\non the floor, so we had sex three times.
嗯哈
Sure.
然后 今早我走的时候\n我们亲吻了
And then, this morning\nbefore I left for we kissed.
哦 太奇怪了
Ooh, that's weird.
太奇怪了
That is weird.
是吧? 这个吻毁了我们的约法三章
Right? That kiss violated the\nspirit of our whole arrangement.
我是说 \n她可能会觉得我开始对她有感觉了
I meanI mean, she probably thinks\nI'm getting feelings for her.
那么 你是不是真这样呢?
Well, are you?
没错 我爱上她了
Yes, I'm in love with her.
这不是你要说的--\n是说你啦 伙计
Is what you--\nThat's you, dude.
不 这不能代表什么
No. It didn't mean anything.
这只是我们作为恋人时余留下来的\n条件反射罢了
It was just some leftover reflex\nfrom when we were a couple.
但我还以为我早就忘得干净了
But I think I probably blew it.
当然咯 一切都~结束了
Definitely. It is so over.
等等 也许Robin觉得这不奇怪呢
Hold the phone. Maybe Robin\ndidn't think it was weird.
这太奇怪了 很奇怪 奇怪 奇怪
It was weird. Weird,\nweird, weird, weird, weird.
C-i G-u-a-i
奇怪
W-I-E-R-D.\nWeird.
'奇怪"可不是这么拼的T
That's not how you spell "weird."
好啦 Lily \n你可别学Ted啥都这么计较
Come on, Lily. Nobody likes a Ted.
我提醒过你的
I tried to warn you.
一旦"旧情复燃'\n就会有人被烧到的
When exes relapse,\nsomeone always gets hurt.
但没人听我的 总是这样的遭遇
But no one listened. Story of my life.
我可爱的外表让大家不相信我的忠谏
My cuteness interferes with\npeople hearing my message.
那么 我该怎么办呢?
Well, what should I do?
只有一个办法
There's only one thing to do.
你俩不能再上床了 求你们了
You have to stop\nsleeping together, please.
我觉得我们不能再上床了
I think we have to\nstop sleeping together.
我和Ted 就像吸烟一样
With me and Ted, it's like cigarettes.
你酒醉了 吸一只 觉得没事
You have one when you're\ndrunk and you think it's fine.
但到你发现时\n你一周都要买一箱的烟了
But before you know it,\nyou're buying a carton a week.
我觉得我要结束这种状况了
I think I have to end it.
没错 我要结束这种状况了
Yup. I have to end it.
那么... 我们以后不这样了 对吧?
So... We're ending it, huh?
对的 没错
I think so, yeah.
这样对彼此都好
It's probably for the best.
- 那样很好 但我不想觉得别扭\n- 我也是
- It was fun, but I don't want things to get weird.\n- Me neither.
- 只当室友?\n- 只当室友
- Roomies?\n- Roomies.
Robin!\nRobin!
咱别跟别人说 好吗?
But we tell no one. Deal?
- 一言为定\n- 一言为定
- Deal.\n- Deal.
- 伙计!\n- 够了!
- Dude!\n- Come on!
你俩怎么回事啊?
What is the matter with you?
买那个
That one.
但是 这次是草草了事的
So, that didn't last long.
顺便一问 Marshall \n你在我们的公寓里干嘛啊?
By the way, Marshall, what were\nyou doing back in our apartment?
我还以为你找到完美的地方了
I thought you had the perfect situation.
确实是
I did.
一切都进展得很顺利
Everything was going great.
我觉得很舒服 自信满满
I was feeling more\ncomfortable, more confident.
我觉得自己可以掌握世界
I felt I could take on the world.
一天早晨 我拿了本杂志下到8楼去
One morning, I took my magazine\ndown to the eighth floor.
我们要把这屋都整修一番
We gotta gut this whole place.
我们要把这面墙的这处和那处砸开
I need these walls\ntaken out here and here.
- 你说得对\n- 好了
- You got it.\n- All right.
名人都热衷自己拿干洗的衣服?
Celebrities pick up their dry cleaning?
我也是哦 \n别砸进来!
I pick up my dry\ncleaning. Don't come in!
所以那种飘飘然感觉没持续多久
So that didn't last long.
- 哦 多谢\n- 你在干嘛?
- Oh, thanks.\n- What are you doing?
哦 既然这些室友间鸡毛蒜皮的琐事\n让你和Robin之间起摩擦
Oh, well, since all these roomie squabbles are\nstill causing friction between you and Robin,
我想我能帮下忙
I thought I'd help out.
哦 顺便说一下\n我今天去了趟邮局
Oh, BTW, I went by\nthe post office today.
我给你买了些邮票
I picked you up some stamps.
1万枚 这应该够你用了
Here's ten thousand. That oughta do ya.
好吧 多谢 我想够了
Um, okay. Thanks, I guess.
- 嘿 你要喝啤酒吗?\n- 好的
- Hey, uh, you want a beer?\n- Okay.
没错 我顺路买的\n别客气
Yeah, I picked those up on\nthe way over. It was nothing.
你给我们买了个洗碗机?
Did you buy us a dishwasher?
没有 这个洗碗机本来就有的\n你在这儿住了多久了?
No. That dishwasher's always been\nthere. How long have you lived here?
那么 你做这些\n就是为了阻止我跟Robin吵架啊?
So, you're doing all this to keep\nme and Robin from fighting, huh?
事实上 我很担心你们
Exactly. I worry about you two.
我和Robin上床让你不爽了 对吧?
It bothers you that Robin and\nI are hooking up, doesn't it?
没有 没有的事 你真扯
No. Not at all. That's crazy.
干嘛?
What?
你爱上Robin了?
Are you in love with Robin?
你竟然爱上Robin了
You're in love with Robin.
这就是你为啥不愿我俩搞在一起
That's why you don't want us hooking up.
什么? 这真是荒谬的问话
What? That is crazy talk.
我作为你兄弟就不能像其他兄弟们一样\n给你收拾房间吗?
Can't a bro clean another\nbro's apartment like bros do?
给我说出一个这样干过的兄弟名字
Name me one bro in the history\nof bros who has ever done that.
我能说出2个: \n清洁工先生和Belvedere清洁剂
I'll name two: Misters\nClean and Belvedere.
听着 我和Robin的事 \n都是闹着玩儿的
Look, this thing with me and\nRobin, it's totally casual.
如果你告诉我你对她有感觉\n我也不会怎么样的
I'm not gonna freak out if you\ntell me you have feelings for her.
那么 你对她有感觉吗?
So, do you?
不 不 我没有 我没有\n不 我没有 我没有 不
No. No, I don't. I don't,\nno. I don't. I don't. No.
Robin一直都是你的 伙计\n祝你俩愉快
Robin is all yours,\ndude. Have fun with her.
现在 如果你不介意的话\n我要去睡别的女孩儿了
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm\ngonna go sleep with other girls.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
- 对!\n- 肯定?
- Yes!\n- Positive?
当然
Absolutely.
然后我冲出去了
And then I stormed out.
我为啥要那么做?
Why did I do that?
我的意思是 也许这得追溯到我老爸\n但是...
I mean, maybe it goes back\nto my father issues, but...
我给最好的哥们许可证\n让他跟我心爱的女孩上床
I basically gave my best friend license\nto have sex with the girl of my dreams.
我毁了自己
I totally sabotaged myself.
现在我还抽烟了 我抽烟了
And now I'm smoking. Now I'm smoking.
滚出去
Get out.
但是这是我的分享时间哎\n我还拿着分享感受小熊呢
But it's feelings hour and I'm\nholding Feely the Share Bear.
谁拿到了"分享感受小熊"\n谁就得坐到椅子上说故事
And whoever's holding Feely the Share\nBear gets to sit in the share chair.
Barney
这可不是你的私人医生的办公室啊
Barney, this is not your\nprivate therapist's office.
这些孩子也有故事要说呢\n你该晓得的
These kids have issues to\ntalk about, too, you know.
Ben的父母要离婚了
Ben's parents are getting divorced.
真的?
They are?
谁想画蜡笔画啊?
Who wants to do some coloring?
哦 很好 是Lily派你来的?
Oh, great, did Lily send you?
我没拿那只小熊 好吧?
I don't have the bear, okay?
我不会还回去的!
I'm not giving it back!
你是在笑吗?
Why are you smiling?
哦 我只是... 读了一本杂志
Oh, I just... read a magazine.
上班的时候
Here at work.
- 什么?\n- 没错 这真是最棒的事了
- What?\n- Yeah. It's the funniest thing.
当时我在上网 查酒店的价钱\n突然我意识到一个问题
I was online, looking up rates for\nhotels when I realized something.
这样太蠢了
This is stupid.
我决定抛开手头的活儿\n去做我想做的事
I decided it was time to let go of my\nhang-ups and do the thing I gotta do
在我做了这个决定后\n一切都变了
and once I made that\ndecision, everything changed.
这年轻人敢于承担他的所作所为
There's a young man who's\ncomfortable with who he is.
我知道你要做什么\n我尊敬你的行为
I know what you're about to\ndo and I respect you for it.
嘿  Eriksen 去远点的地儿看去
Hey, Eriksen. Go the distance.
Marshall 今天你跨出了勇敢的一步
Marshall, you made a brave step today.
记住莎士比亚说的:\n美德是勇敢的 为善则无所畏惧
Remember what Shakespeare wrote: Virtue\nis bold, and goodness never fearful.
你说的没错 你这个我老婆跟我提过千回
You're right, Super Hot Lady Who My Wife Keeps\nTelling Me Why You're Famous But I Keep Forgetting.
但我还是忘了你为何出名的超级性感小妞\n(封面是金・卡戴珊 当今美国最红的性感宝贝 \n 是帕丽斯・希尔顿的闺密)
- 咱就干吧\n- 请带路吧
- Let's do this.\n- Lead the way.
哇 Marshall 恭喜你啊
Wow, Marshall. Congratulations.
多谢 我最后不得不这么做
Thanks. I was gonna\nhave to do it eventually.
你知道 有时你必须... \n你必须要男人一点...
You know, sometimes you just\ngotta... you gotta man up and...
勇敢地去试试
and just go for it.
Marshall 我要走了
Marshall, I have to go.
哦 顺便一提\n我这儿有个洗手间 你爱用就用
Oh, by the way, I have a bathroom\nhere if you ever want to use it.
你个够娘养...
Son of a...
Ted 我要告诉你真相
Ted, I have to tell you the truth.
我爱上了... 墨西哥夹饼
I'm in love with... tacos.
- 你要干嘛? \n- 我  倒点垃圾啊
- What are you doing? - I'm,\nuh, taking out the triz-ash.
如果你啊 要找Ted的话 他出去了
If you're, uh, looking for Ted, he left.
还有 ... 我们之间的约定也结束了\n顺带一说
And, uh... our little arrangement\nis, uh, over, by the way.
真的? 那真是太帅...衰了
Really? That's aws... ful.
- 太帅衰了?\n- 没错 就是太帅衰了
- Awfsful?\n- Yeah, it's just awfsful.
怎么回事?
What happened?
啊 是他坚持的
Ah, he just insisted.
他说他不能这样做\n因为有人会伤心的
He said he couldn't do it anymore\nbecause someone's gonna get hurt.
我想我们都知道他说的谁吧
I think we all know\nwho he meant by that.
是吗?
Do we?
这不是很明显了吗?
Isn't it obvious?
- 是吗?\n- 没错
- Is it?\n- Yeah.
就是Ted他自己啊 \n你也知道他是个浪漫主义者
It's Ted. You know\nwhat a romantic he is.
他根本没法区分肉欲与精神之爱
He can't separate the\nphysical from the emotional.
- 他就像是...\n- 我爱你
- He's all like...\n- I love you.
实际上 他跟你不一样 你知道吧?
Exactly. He's not like you, you know?
而且 我们是朋友啊
Besides, we're friends.
我可不想陷进去\n把事情搞砸了
I don't want to screw that\nup by getting involved.
跟朋友约会不会有好结果的
Dating friends never works out.
那么 你想去吃墨西哥夹饼?
So, uh, you want to get a taco?
墨西哥夹饼?
A taco?
你爱吃啊 忘啦?
You love them, remember?
没错
Right.
来吧 我饿了
Come on, I'm hungry.
所以我和Robin又恢复到单纯室友的身份\n一切回归正常
So Robin and I went back to just being\nroommates and things went back to normal.
你们的Lily阿姨说的没错
Your Aunt Lily was right.
当两位旧情人旧情复燃时\n有人会受伤了
When two exes decide to just be\ncasual, someone always gets hurt.
虽然说的并不是我们俩
It just wasn't one of us.